Haha, let's go out.
あはは、出ちゃうね
Is it a little more like this?
もうちょっとこっちかな?
Can't move?
動けない?
It's out.
出ちゃった
Are you behind me?
後ろ向こうか
I feel like we are the same.
ひとしい気がする
Can I put it in?
入れてもいい?
Okay, I'll ask you to follow me more.
よし、もっとついてくださいって言ってもらおう
Okay, please follow me more.
よし、もっとついてください
Facing the front.
正面向いて
Same.
ひとしい
Please come out to your master.
ご主人様に出てください
What?
何を?
They come out of the area without their master's permission.
ご主人様のうっきなうちに地辺を出てくる
It was expensive.
かったりしたな
It's becoming a rescue ship.
助け船になってるぞ
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ
Can I go?
行っていい?
Oh, let's go.
ああ、行く
I liked this hotel.
ここのホテル、気に入った
That way?
そっち?
I think I'll banish you again.
また追放にしようかな
See you then.
じゃあ、また